Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series C. Presorted Photos
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 4)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Albert Trotman, Karl Crutchfield, Klytus, Delilah McKavish, Peterkin Photo, Barbara Matthews, Dale Leifeste, Allen Morgan, Austin Hansen, Juanita M. Cole, Star Black,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 5)
    Photographer if identified: Gideon Manasseh, Curt Clemons, Nick Baretta, George Frye, Jonathan Shorey, Bill Moore, Lynda Downey, Jean Pagliuso, Austin Hansen, Karl Crutchfield
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 6)
    Also 2 halftone prints, 1 laser print. 6 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: South Light Studio, Tom Matthews, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Don Hamerman, Kenn Duncan, Toni Parks, Eric Roth, Klytus,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 7)
    5 prints have staples through edge. One print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Photos by Luigi, Pictorial Enterprise, Monroe S. Frederick II, Kate Kunz, Lawrence Ivy, Lem Peterkin,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 8)
    Also 2 velox prints. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to recto, 2 prints have press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Harlee Little, Shelley Brown, George Spence, Bill Moore, James Gilbert, Allen Morgan, Johan Elbers, Don Hunstein, Bert Andrews, Peterkin Photo,
    Number of Prints: 50
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 9)
    Photographer if identified: George West, Pictorial Enterprise, Karl Crutchfield, Kim Robinson, Sharon McNeill, Don Moss, Austin Hansen, Bill Pryor,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 10)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Wali Amin Muhammad, Karl Crutchfield, Larry Busacca, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Vincent Frye, Peterkin Photo, Austin Hansen, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Arla Beck
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 11)
    Also postcard for Hakim Mutlaq exhibition, flier for Audrey Palmer Hawks scholarship fund. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Dave Greene, Bernard Fallon,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 12)
    Photographer if identified: Carol Anstett, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Martha Politarjos, Karl Crutchfield, Wayne Roland, Peterkin Photo, Louis Boone, Pach Bros., John Crow, Joe Vericker,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 13)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Wali Amin Muhammad, Bert Andrews, Blanche Mackey, Peterkin Photo, H.L. Delgado, Sean Galvin, Karl Crutchfield, Bonnie Schiffman, Bill Moore, Donovan Gopie
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 14)
    Also 1 halftone print, 1 print from magazine. 3 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: NASA, Kerika Fields, Bert Andrews, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Lawrence Berman, Karl Crutchfield, Louis Boone, Eddie Paylor, Peterkin Photo, Mansa K. Mussa
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 15)
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Alex Summers, Pictorial Enterprise, Karl Crutchfield, Abe Ginsberg, Popsie, Michael Jacobs, Curt Clemons, Gary Gershoff,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 16)
    Also 1 halftone print, flier for Women in Dance. 1 print is a composite of two. 1 print has press release stapled to recto. 1 print has ms. Leaf stapled to recto. 3 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, L. Banks, Randee St. Nicholas, Bob Greene, Pictorial Enterprise, Jack Deutch, Rich Pipeling, Teixeira Nash,
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 17)
    Also postcard for Harlem Renaissance Day of Commitment, 3 photos from magazines, 1 4"x5" negative. 3 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Lynda Downey, Juanita M. Cole, Albert Trotman, Hugh Bell, T. Kan, Bill Sparrow, Carol Rosegg, Allen Morgan, Eric Stephen Jacobs, Kwame Brathwaite, Pictorial Enterprise, Gerald Peart, Gustav Heningburg
  - H (Box C-5, Folder 18)
    Also Mass card for Adelaide Hall. 8 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Lynda Downey, Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Peterkin Photo, Bruce Talamon, Gill Photographers, Geoff Wilde, Barry Sullivan, Lem Peterkin, Bill Moore, Boris Barcaly, Bryan D. Hall, Sam Samuels, Harris Photo
  - I (has a large amount of "J" subjects) (Box C-5, Folder 19)
    Photographer if identified: Melissa Moseley, Myles Aronwitz, Tony Allen, Pictorial Enterprise, Alexander J. Allen, Peterkin Photo, Bill Price, Diane Bondareff, Phoebe Ferguson, Lem Peterkin, Randee St. Nicholas, Catrina Wessel, Carol Friedman, James J. Kriegsmann, Gary Gershoff, Jeffrey Scales, Bill Moore
  - I (Box C-5, Folder 20)
    Also one velox print. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Matthew Rolston, John Isaac, A. Hansen, Pictorial Enterprise, Merrill A. Roberts, Jessica Katz, Phoebe Ferguson, Mitch Goldberg, Curt Clemons
  - I (Box C-5, Folder 21)
    Also laser print. 3 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons, Flora S. Kaplan, Pictorial Enterprise, Don Hunstein, Gary Heery, Shelley Brown, Mitch Goldberg, Jack Hoffman
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 22)
    Also 1 photocopy. 7 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons, Carmen de Jesus, André N. Beckles, Harris Photo, Lem Peterkin, Saphier Studio, Joan Tedeschi,
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 23)
    Also 3 halftone prints. 4 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Michael Ahearn, Hakim Mutlaq, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Tatum Photo, Ankers, Anderson & Cutts, Gerald Peart, James Gilbert, Sam Samuels, Karl Crutchfield, Curt Clemons, Miller Photography
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 24)
    Photographer if identified: Ruby Washington, Bryan D. Hall, Bill Moore, Tom Casino, Bert Andrews, Pictorial Enterprise, Carol Rosegg, Curt Clemons, Karl Crutchfield, L. St. Clair Dummett, Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo, Edwin Pagan
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 25)
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Chris Griffith, Karl Crutchfield, Allen Morgan, Pictorial Enterprise, Gerald Peart,
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 26)
    Also 1 color halftone print. 7 prints have staples through edge. Photo of Yolanda Joyner is inscribed on back to her mother.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Ron Tom, Joe Grant, Frank Carroll, Joan Vitale Strong, Joel Gordon, Hakim Mutlaq, Bob Head, Istvan Bathoryi, Cleveland Davies, Karl Crutchfield, Tex Harris,
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 27)
    Also 1 photo cut from magazine, One halftone print. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Amelia V. Panico, Michael Jacobs, Karl Crutchfield, Lensman, Lem Peterkin, James J. Kriegsmann, Tom Parks, Larry Brown, P.J. Albert,
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 28)
    Also photocopy. 6 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to recto.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Joel Gordon, Darrell Fitzgerald, Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo, Bill Carter, Juanita M. Cole, Monroe S. Frederick II, Danie Hastings, Karl Crutchfield, John Pruski, Curt Clemons, Coreen Simpson,
  - J (Box C-5, Folder 29)
    Photographer if identified: Arnold Turner
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 30)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Coreen Simpson, Don West, Photos by Luigi, Monroe S. Frederick II, Curt Clemons, Maam Cher Kan, Harris Photo, Lem Peterkin, Shelley Brown, Sharon Stern
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 31)
    Also one halftone print. 7 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Juanita M. Cole, Sean Butler, Allen Morgan,
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 32)
    Booklet on The Spirit of Kujichagulia, color halftone of Moammar Quaddafi removed from a calendar. 5 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Howard Atlee, Bert Andrews, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Gary Heery, Curt Clemons, Robert Cohen, Standard Studios, Edward Reed,
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 33)
    Also 1 photocopy. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann,
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 34)
    Also photo from magazine. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Johnny Buzzerio, J. Lash, Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo, Jeffrey Henson Scales, Michael Biondo, Eddie Paylor, Gerald E. Hayes, Variety Moszynski, Joan Vitale Strong, Kenn Duncan
  - K (Box C-5, Folder 35)
    Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Harlee Little, Dan Ochiva, H.L. Delgado, Thomas Victor, Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons, Juanita M. Cole, J. Lash, Gerald Peart,
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 1)
    1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 3 prints have staples through edge. 1 Polaroid print.
    Photographer if identified: Barry Kramer/Jos. Abeles Studio, Pictorial Enterprise, Gene Luttenberg, Peterkin Photo, Terrance Carney, Lisa Leavitt, Gary Heery, Thomasine Barton-Gangadean, Kate Kunz, Juanita M. Cole, Board of Ed. City of New York, Austin Hansen,
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 2)
    Also 3 photocopies, 1 postcard from KISS-FM. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Bill Price, Marlis Momber, Peterkin Photo, Hakim Mutlaq, Elissa Rubin,
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 3)
    4 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto. 1 ms. Leaf. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Karl Crutchfield, Lem Peterkin,
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 4)
    Also card for Gladys Knight show. 6 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Marvin Cole, Karl Crutchfield, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Allen Morgan, Joan Vitale Strong, Jim Romano, James J. Kriegsmann, Carol Friedman, Paula M. Lerner, Bert Andrews, Eileen Polk, Randee St. Nicholas, Juanita M. Cole
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 5)
    5 prints have staples through edge. 1 Polaroid print. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Carol Friedman, Darius Anthony, Peterkin Photo, Paul Natkin, Chase Roe, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Price, Studio One, Donald J. Brophy, Ernest Paniccioli, Bill May, Harriet Hoffman, Bill Moore, Tony Esparza, Kate Kunz, Joan Vitale Strong
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 6)
    1 print has press release stapled to verso. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has caption stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Willard Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Spencer A. Burnett, Larry Busacca, Yousuf Karsh, Maurice Seymour, Jack Vartoogian, Gary Heery, Jeffrey Scales, Karen Epstein, Ron West
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 7)
    2 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to recto.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Harris Photo, Curt Clemons, Robert Cohen, Adrian Boot, Rhonda Wiles, Mara Kurtz, Robert Lewis, Mark Seliger, Popsie, Carmen L. de Jesus,
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 8)
    1 print has press release stapled to verso. 4 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: Claude Rolo, Jeff Katz, Bruce Williams, Pictorial Enterprise, Zack Lewis, Laura Muzio/Jim Sousa, William L. Ballinger, Jeffrey Scales, Eugene Pinkowski, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield
  - K (Box C-6, Folder 9)
    Also one halftone print. 7 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints stapled together. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Kwame Brathwaite, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Portfolio International, Michele Clement, Photo by Luigi, Bert Andrews, Holland Wemple, Harris Photo, Lloyd Yearwood,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 10)
    Also one halftone print. 4 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Henry Grossman, Pictorial Enterprise, Kenton, Juanita M. Cole, Michael Benabib, Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons, Bruno of Hollywood, Ira Berger, Marc Raboy, Janette Beckman, Lem Peterkin, Hubert Van Stephens, Karl Crutchfield, Elena Borstein
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 11)
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, Marbeth, James Gilbert, Karl Crutchfield, Joe Pineiro, Bob Greene, Michael Grecco, Karl Schumacher, Larry Fine,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 12)
    Also photo from newspaper. 3 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Hakim, Karl Crutchfield, Joan Penn, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Bill Moore, Helen Levitt, Rita E. Henderson, Robert F. Holden,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 13)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo, Miller Photography, David Lee
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 14)
    Also one halftone print. 8 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Deborah Feingold, Peterkin Photo, Juanita M. Cole, George Ligon, R. Gregoire,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 15)
    Also 1 photocopy. 7 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto. 2 prints have press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: George Dureau, E. Lee White, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Lester Cohen, Burt Glinn, Pictorial Enterprise, Ethan Russell, Ron West, David Lee, Curt Clemons, Chelsea Photographers
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 16)
    Also 2 photos from magazine, 1 halftone print,. 2 prints stapled together, with press release on verso. 1 print with press release stapled to recto. 2 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Caroline Greyshock, Curt Clemons, Stephan Apicella-Hitchcock, Davis Factor, Renaldo Jackson, Nat Valentine, Able Abel, Dan Helms, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Darius Anthony, Sue Kwon, Mercedes Lewis, James Gilbert, The Lensman,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 17)
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Joseph Major, Ken Nahoum, Curt Clemons, Moneta Sleet Jr., Marc Raboy, James J. Kriegsmann, Bruce Williams, Deborah Feingold, Peter Ashworth, Simon Fowler, Harris Photo,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 18)
    Also one velox print. 1 print has press release stapled to recto. 2 prints stapled together. 3 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Marc Raboy, Ken Nahoum, Ira Block, Shelley Brown, Pictorial Enterprise, Lena Brisman, Aaron Smith Jr., Pach Bros., Peterkin Photo,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 19)
    1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 4 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo, Jean Jacques Perreau, Harris Photo, Bill Moore, Christopher Little, Rapid News Service/Burley, Juanita M. Cole, Joe Grant, Burt Glinn, Marc Raboy,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 20)
    Also 1 postcard. 4 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Doug Hawthorne, Bill Whiting, Charles Ford, Lloyd Yearwood, United Press International, JWL, Carol Rosegg, Mike Jones, Juanita M. Cole
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 21)
    7 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Bob Head, Karl Crutchfield, Ralph Baker, Peterkin Photo, Howie Evans, Palmisano, Marc Raboy
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 22)
    7 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: Kwame Brathwaite, Juanita M. Cole, Elaine Tomlin, Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, John Bellissimo, Mike Miyata, Allen Morgan, Karl Crutchfield
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 23)
    Also press releases. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 24)
    Also 2 halftone prints. 9 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Caroline Greyshock, Pictorial Enterprise, Arthur Crosinsky, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Harris Photo, Maxine's Classic Photography,
  - L (Box C-6, Folder 25)
    Also one halftone print. 2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Loristan Studios, Pictorial Enterprise, Larry Brown, Shelley Brown, Juanita M. Cole, Queens Borough President, Caroline Greyshock, Waring Abbott, Melodie Gimple, Shelley Brown, Alle Beaulieu, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Todd Gray, Lloyd Yearwood, Lem Peterkin, Harris Photo
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 26)
    Also 1 halftone print, 1 velox print, 1 print from newspaper, 2 prints from magazine. photocopy of memorial service for John William McDonald. 5 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Carol Rosegg, Curt Clemons, Eddie Paylor, Gordon Parks, William Ballinger, Michael A. McKay, Stan Williams, James Gilbert, Peterkin Photo, Eli Weinberg, Kwame Brathwaite, Rosemarie Borland, George West, Bill Moore
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 27)
    Photographer if identified: Bob Marshall, James Gilbert, Garth Morgan, Curt Clemons, Bill Moore, Goddy WichenDu C., Karl Crutchfield, Anthony Barboza, Christian Steiner, Ken Nahoum, Joanne Savio, Richard Laird, Peterkin Photo, King Photographers, James Gilbert,
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 28)
    4 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has ms. Caption stapled to recto.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Allen Morgan, Aaron Rapoport, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Ron Angle
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 29)
    Also 1 postcard. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has ms. caption stapled to recto.
    Photographer if identified: Jessica Pohly, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Juanita M. Cole, Peterkin Photo, Sam Reiss, Gerald Peart, Karen Carrillo, Karl Crutchfield, Lem Peterkin, Arthur Krasinsky, Bill Moore, William Coupon, James Gilbert,
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 30)
    Also 1 halftone print and one laser print. 7 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Jerry Marshall, Wali Amin Muhammad, Peterkin Photo, Danny Dowson, Karl Crutchfield, Lem Peterkin, Henry Diltz, George DuBose, James J. Kriegsmann, Jonathan Atkin, Bill Moore,
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 31)
    Photographer if identified: Kathryn Kirk, Tony Cordoza, Jan Persson, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise,
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 32)
    1 print has press release stapled to verso. 4 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Herbert Ascherman Jr., Glenn J. Davis, Pictorial Enterprise, Bryan D. Hall, James Gilbert, Joe Vericker, Kwame Brathwaite, Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Lynn Goldsmith, Millie Burns
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 33)
    Photographer if identified: Hakim Mutlaq, Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Wali Amin Muhammad, Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, H.L. Delgado, Bill Moore, Christian Steiner, Allen Morgan, Curt Clemons, Brian Leng, Donna Ann McAdams, Gray
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 34)
    Also large booklet "Chronology of Events...at Applecrest." 2 prints have staples through edge. 1 print mounted to cardboard.
    Photographer if identified: Lois Greenfield, Jeff Katz, Peterkin Photo, Toshi, Nevill Garrick, Joe Grant, David Gahr, Ernesto Browne, Pictorial Enterprise, Bruce Talamon, Williams Stambler, Ken Love, Wali Amin Muhammad,
  - M (Box C-6, Folder 35)
    Also magazine article. 7 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
    Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach, Pictorial Enterprise, Larry Lettera, Karl Crutchfield, Allen Morgan, Lem Peterkin, Rodney K. Hurley, Peterkin Photo, Phyllis Cuington
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 1)
    Also 2 halftone prints, news article. 4 prints have staples through edge. 1 Polaroid integral print.
    Photographer if identified: Eric Heinila, Robert Cohen, James J. Kriegsmann, Lynn Goldsmith, Janette Beckman, Beverly Parker, King Douglas, Martha Swope, Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Hakim Mutlaq, Pictorial Enterprise, Kim Robinson, Weathers Productions, Karl Crutchfield
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 2)
    Also 1 postcard for Nayobe, One halftone print. 5 prints have staples through edge. 1 Polaroid print.
    Photographer if identified: D. B. Forer, Donna Decesare, James J. Kriegsmann, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, Buzz Feitshans IV, Peterkin Photo, Winnie Klotz, Juanita M. Cole, Jim Shea, Carol Weinburg, Robert Lewis,
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 3)
    Photographer if identified: Carlan Studio, Rebecca Lesher, Karl Crutchfield, George West, Peterkin Photo, Carol Rosegg,
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 4)
    Also 1 inkjet print, fax of Newsweek cover. 2 prints have press release stapled to verso. 2 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Carter, Christian Steiner, Darius Anthony, Erik Heinila, Ed Edahl, Juanita M. Cole, Ebet Roberts, Mara Kurtz, Thomans H. Wirth, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Lawrence W. Jackson,
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 5)
    2 prints mounted on cardboard with ms. Note. One print has staple through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Donna DeCesare, Allen Morgan,
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 6)
    Photographer if identified: Darius Anthony, Pictorial Enterprise, Shelley Brown, Greg Heiser, Coreen Simpson, Bryan D. Hall, Marc Raboy, Bill Price, Bill Moore, Chester Higgins Jr., James J. Kriegsmann, Eric Heinila
  - N (Box C-7, Folder 7)
    Also 1 postcard. 4 prints have staples through edge.
    Photographer if identified: Hayden Roger Celestin, William L. Ballinger, Nate Silverstein, Pictorial Enterprise, Lem Peterkin, James Heffernan, Shelley Brown, David Booker, Bill Moore, Nancy Miller Elliott,
  - O (Box C-7, Folder 8)
    Also newspaper clipping. 4 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Aimo, King Photographers, Bill King, Pictorial Enterprise, Lloyd Yearwood, Shelley Brown, Bobby Holland, Mike Jones, Martha Swope, Bert Andrews,
  - O (Box C-7, Folder 9)
    2 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has press release stapled to verso. 2 Polaroid prints.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Allen Morgan, James J. Kriegsmann, Juanita M. Cole, Susan Ortega & Max Schwartz, Howard T. Cash, Bob Head, Shelley Brown, Bryan D. Hall, Mark "Weissguy" Weiss,
  - O (Box C-7, Folder 10)
    7 prints have staples through edge. 1 laser print. 1 print has press release stapled to verso. 1 print has news article stapled to verso.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Don Perdue, George Hurrell,
  - O (Box C-7, Folder 11)
    6 prints have staples through edge. Bio of Dan Owens
    Photographer if identified: Larry Kodani, Herbert Hawkins, Susan Lerner, Wali Amin Muhammad, Edward Reed, Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Pictorial Enterprise, Jessica Katz, George West
  - O (Box C-7, Folder 12)
    2 prints have staples through edge. 1 Polaroid copy print. 1 print has press release stapled to recto.